forestlaneshul.com 2015-06-02

# Privacy and Terms

#### Privacy and Terms

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at _admin@forestlaneshul.com_.

At www.forestlaneshul.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.forestlaneshul.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.forestlaneshul.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Forestlaneshul.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
**  
DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.forestlaneshul.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.forestlaneshul.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
1\. Google Adsense  
2\. Amazon  
3\. Others

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.forestlaneshul.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Forestlaneshul.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.forestlaneshul.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Other Notes:**

[Forestlaneshul.com](http://www.forestlaneshul.com/) collects Name, Email and Website information from anyone who leaves a comment on the website. Once the comment is approved, the Name and the Website information, along with the comment contents will be visible to everyone. However your email submitted inside the Email field will not be shared with anyone else.

We advise our visitors not to publish their personal emails inside the comment content. We also advise our visitors not to publish any personal information or sensitive data in the comments. In case of violation of these terms, we are not responsible for the misuse of these data whatsoever.

Apart from the information provided by the visitors themselves on the website, our servers also automatically record the browsing data from our visitors for analytical purposes. Apart from that, we do not collect any other information from our visitors.

The contents of the comments available on the website are provided by our visitors. The information contained in these contents are not verified and visitors are strongly advised to do their own research before taking any decision based on these information.

For details on how we serve information and news articles on this website, Please read our [Disclaimer](http://www.forestlaneshul.com/disclaimer/).
